[Music]
yeah
okay
okay okay yeah yeah yeah look me vers
you and you know they picking cheap and
expensive you know the difference you
know that it's Tak you know what it's
giv Hair Nails Port bear I can survive
in the coldest conditions ho L they T
when they spin [ __ ] is washed soap in
the dishes I apply pressure like B
constrictors one [ __ ] two [ __ ] old
[ __ ] New [ __ ] none of Y [ __ ] is not
going to do [ __ ] I'm in Miami I pull up
on cruise ship you in Miami for all room
[ __ ] when I step is stamped foot on neck
can't
Brey CLE Diamond my ling up I'm like
what in the [ __ ] if you scared then just
say that whole enough is enough they was
just in my DM say no trust in these Luts
I'm about to call a diamond [ __ ] n if
you linking up I'm like what in the [ __ ]
if you scared then just say that enough
is enough they was just in my DM say no
trusting these SLS I'm about to call up
Diamond [ __ ] n if you B I'm like o
child cool down too high too wild Mo
clear new style how you [ __ ] with me
girl give me one shot and I'm raising
the glass give me two shots I'm shaking
this ass give me three shots and I'm
ready to [ __ ] five four shots I be ready
to Splash give it to me so I got to pop
it I'm sending on business I'm ready
body [ __ ] be talking I be big in they
pocket girl tell me about I'm l I'm
pretty I'm running the city I'm [ __ ]
on [ __ ] in every Department this ass
T thick like peanut butter [ __ ] jelly
body there a lot of winning a lot of
score cardi BR cardi Jordan these
[ __ ] all losers they can't do is not
important look he I'm getting better and
better I do not see no competitors you
know the gang hit that [ __ ] said it was
regular see me fighting see me in F see
me with money these [ __ ] is bugging
either these [ __ ] blind or I'm
invisible [ __ ] can't see me at night
when I H I was stamped putot on neck
can't bre luy charm CLE Diamond I see my
eyes linking up I'm like what in the
[ __ ] if you scared then just say that
whole enough is enough they was just in
my DM a no trust in these Luts I'm about
to call up Diamond [ __ ] n if you
linking up I'm like what in the [ __ ] if
you scared then just say that whole
enough is enough they was just in my DM
say no trust in these Luts I'm about to
call up Diamond B n if you